And finally, in tonight's news, a 9 -year -old boy named Joe, told not to draw in
class, lands a job decorating a restaurant with his drawings.
Rather than shutting down the habit of drawing in his school's workbook,
Joe's parents decided to encourage his creativity by sending their son to an after
-school art class.
Rather than shutting down the habit of drawing in his school's workbook,
Joe's parents decided to encourage his creativity by sending their son to an after
-school art class.
His teacher recognized Joe's talent and posted all his work online, which led to
something pretty wonderful.
His teacher recognized Joe's talent and posted all his work online,
which led to something pretty wonderful.
A restaurant named Number 4 in Newcastle contacted Joe's teacher to ask if the 9
-year -old could come and decorate its dining room with his drawings.
Every day after school, Joe's dad drives him to the restaurant so he can put his
ideas straight on the wall.